<odoo>
    <data>
        <!--Processes-->
        <record id="sales_process" model="risk_management.business_process">
            <field name="name">Sales</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    This process is aimed at initiating and supporting the identification and evaluation of likely customers (prospects),
                    sales presentation, and successful conclusion of sales activities. It requires a close coordination
                    of people, equipment, tools, and techniques, and includes advertising and promotion.
                </p>
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="delivery_process" model="risk_management.business_process">
            <field name="name">Product / service delivery</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    The delivery process is aimed at controlling, packaging and shipping of goods sold to the destination chosen by the
                    customer, in the best conditions of time and costs.
                </p>
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="hiring_process" model="risk_management.business_process">
            <field name="name">Employee Development &amp; Satisfaction (Human Resources)</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    Mainly the completely HR Process look into complete controlling and smooth performance of employees
                    and management and their relationship with the clients.
                </p>
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="quality_process" model="risk_management.business_process">
            <field name="name">Quality, Process Improvement &amp; Change Management</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    Change Management Processes include a sequence of steps or activities that move a change from
                    inception to delivery. Change Management Plans are developed to support a project to deliver a change.
                    It is typically created during the planning stage of a Change Management Process
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="process_type" eval="'M'"/>
        </record>

        <record id="accounting_process" model="risk_management.business_process">
            <field name="name">Accounting Management</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    The accounting process is three separate types of transactions used to record business transactions
                    in the accounting records. This information is then aggregated into financial statements.
                    The transaction types are as follows:
                </p>
                <ol>
                    <li>The first transaction type is to ensure that reversing entries from the previous period have, in fact, been reversed.</li>
                    <li>The second group is comprised of the steps needed to record individual business transactions in the accounting records.</li>
                    <li>The third group is the period-end processing required to close the books and produce financial statements.</li>
                </ol>
            </field>
            <field name="process_type" eval="'S'"/>
        </record>

        <record id="it_management_process" model="risk_management.business_process">
            <field name="name">Technology Management (Computer &amp; IT)</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    IT management is the process of overseeing all matters related to information technology operations
                    and resources within an IT organization. IT management ensures that all technology resources and associated
                    employees are utilized properly and in a manner that provides value for the organization.
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="process_type" eval="'S'"/>
        </record>

        <record id="finance_management_process" model="risk_management.business_process">
            <field name="name">Financial Analysis, Reporting, &amp; Capital Management</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                   In short, financial management entails planning, organising, controlling, monitoring and evaluating
                    the financial resources of an organisation to achieve its overall objectives.
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="process_type" eval="'M'"/>
        </record>

        <record id="project_charter_dev_process" model="risk_management.business_process">
            <field name="name">Develop Project Charter</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                  This process aim at developing a document that formally authorizes the existence of the project and
                    provides the Project Manager with the authority to apply organizational resources to project activities.
                </p>
                <p>
                    The key benefit of this process is a well-defined project start and project boundaries, creation of a
                    formal record of the project, and a direct way for senior management to formally accept and commit to
                    the project.
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="process_type" eval="'PM'"/>
        </record>

        <!--Process IO-->
        <record id="quote_req_io" model="risk_management.business_process.input_output">
            <field name="name">Request for Quote</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    This is a standard business document we receive from customers, whose purpose is to invite us into a bidding process to bid on
                    specific products or services. RfQ generally means the same thing as Call for bids (CfB) and Invitation for bid (IfB)
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="source_part_cat_id" ref="risk_management.process_partner_cat_customer"/>
            <field name="user_process_ids" eval="[(4, ref('risk_management.sales_process'))]"/>
        </record>

        <record id="purchase_order_io" model="risk_management.business_process.input_output">
            <field name="name">Customer Purchase Order</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    This is a standard commercial document and first official offer issued by a buyer to us
                    indicating types, quantities, and agreed prices for products or services
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="source_part_cat_id" ref="risk_management.process_partner_cat_customer"/>
            <field name="user_process_ids" eval="[(4, ref('risk_management.sales_process'))]"/>
        </record>

        <record id="customer_invoice_io" model="risk_management.business_process.input_output">
            <field name="name">Customer Invoice</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    Standard commercial document send to a buyer listing in detail the services or goods that we sold to the customer.
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="business_process_id" ref="sales_process"/>
            <field name="user_process_ids" eval="[(4, ref('risk_management.delivery_process')), (4, ref('risk_management.accounting_process'))]"/>
            <field name="dest_partner_ids" eval="[(4, ref('risk_management.process_partner_cat_customer'))]"/>
            <field name="ref_input_ids" eval="[(4, ref('risk_management.purchase_order_io'))]"/>
        </record>

        <record id="delivery_form_io" model="risk_management.business_process.input_output">
            <field name="name">Delivery note</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    The delivery note is a document that is given to the customer indicating the quantity and the nature
                    of the goods received by him. It is established at least in 2 signed copies of the parties: the seller
                    or the carrier and the recipient customer.
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="business_process_id" ref="delivery_process"/>
            <field name="user_process_ids" eval="[(4, ref('risk_management.accounting_process'))]"/>
            <field name="dest_partner_ids" eval="[(4, ref('risk_management.process_partner_cat_customer'))]"/>
            <field name="ref_input_ids" eval="[(4, ref('risk_management.customer_invoice_io'))]"/>
        </record>

        <record id="sales_journal_io" model="risk_management.business_process.input_output">
            <field name="name">Sales Journal</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    The sales journal is the prime entry book used in our accounting system to keep track of the sales of items
                that customers(debtors) have purchased on account by charging a receivable on the debit side of an accounts
                receivable account and crediting revenue on the credit side.
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="business_process_id" ref="accounting_process"/>
            <field name="user_process_ids" eval="[(4, ref('risk_management.finance_management_process'))]"/>
            <field name="ref_input_ids" eval="[(4, ref('risk_management.customer_invoice_io'))]"/>
        </record>

        <record id="project_charter_io" model="risk_management.business_process.input_output">
            <field name="name">Project Charter</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    The project charter is the document issued by the project initiator or sponsor that formally authorizes
                    the existence of the project and provides the Project Manager with the authority to apply organizational
                    resources to project activities.
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="business_process_id" ref="project_charter_dev_process"/>

        </record>

        <!-- risk infos -->
        <record id="risk_info_1" model="risk_management.risk.info">
            <field name="risk_category_id" ref="risk_management.risk_cat_1"/>
            <field name="subcategory">Country Risk</field>
            <field name="name">Political instability (risk of war, terrorism, local conflict, attacks ...)</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>Risk of loss of business or profitability outside the company's natural boundary, due to geopolitical instability in the area of presence.</p>
            </field>
            <field name="cause" type="html">
                <p>War, terrorism, local conflict, bombing.</p>
            </field>
            <field name="consequence" type="html">
                <ul>
                    <li>Issues related to the safety of people and property. </li>
                    <li>Loss of turnover and/or profitability. </li>
                    <li>Economic and financial losses.</li>
                    <li>Reputational risk; risk of business failure.</li>
                </ul>
            </field>
            <field name="control" type="html">
               <p>
                   Monitor all geopolitical indicators available, from multiple sources (Ministries, Banks, International Institutions).
                Monitor local and regional situation, implement micromanagement on site.
               </p>
            </field>
            <field name="action" type="html">
                <p>
                    In-depth knowledge of the country concerned and its associated risks.
                Mastering the geopolitical issues of the geographical area of exposure.
                Reduction of the presence, repositioning of critical processes, exit of the zone,
                Avoidance strategy, reduction strategy.
                </p>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="risk_info_2" model="risk_management.risk.info">
            <field name="risk_category_id" ref="risk_management.risk_cat_2"/>
            <field name="subcategory">Cyclical risk</field>
            <field name="name">Unfavorable economic climate impacting the dynamics of the company's activity: inflation, slowdown, GDP decline, unemployment</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>Deteriorating economic conditions for carrying out business activities</p>
            </field>
            <field name="cause" type="html">
                <ul>
                    <li>Economic crisis of local, regional, national or global impact;</li>
                    <li>unemployment, decline in purchasing power B2B or B2C;</li>
                    <li>deterioration of public accounts, over-indebtedness, economic failure of a branch of activity.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="consequence" type="html">
                <ul>
                    <li>Loss of turnover, loss of business opportunities, loss of relative or absolute market shares.</li>
                    <li>Loss business development opportunity.</li>
                    <li>customer insolvency.</li>
                </ul>
            </field>
            <field name="control" type="html">
                <p>
                    Growth rate of the turnover. Turnover rate of the offer. Failure rate on launching new offers. Fine management
                of the company's activity levels (production, storage and consumption cycles)
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="action" type="html">
                <p>
                    Adaptability and flexibility of the strategic and production model of the company: reactivity of the supply
                the evolution of the demand, adaptation of the structure of production and cost of the offer; risk reduction
                strategy to be favored.
                </p>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="risk_info_3" model="risk_management.risk.info">
            <field name="risk_category_id" ref="risk_management.risk_cat_3"/>
            <field name="subcategory">Strategic model</field>
            <field name="name">Poor identification or poor definition of the strategic segments of the strategic business model</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    Incorrect determination of the strategic business model segments to which the commercial offer is deployed.
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="cause" type="html">
                <ul>
                    <li>Bad knowledge of the market.</li>
                    <li>Bad segmentation of customers / prospects database.</li>
                    <li>Mismatch between Commercial offers and market demand.</li>
                </ul>
            </field>
            <field name="consequence" type="html">
                <ul>
                    <li>Inability to market the produced offers on the desired customer segments;</li>
                    <li>Loss of sales, deterioration of the company's economic conditions.</li>
                </ul>
            </field>
            <field name="control" type="html">
                <p>
                    Success rate of the marketing of the offer by strategic segment.
                Number of strategic segments.
                Dimensioning and validated consistency of the strategic business model
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="action" type="html">
                <p>
                    Precise analysis of target market, anticipated segments, and customer profiles making up each strategic segment.
                Precise identification of the specific needs of each client and consistency of the offer that is intended for them.
                Risk circumvention or reduction strategy.
                </p>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="risk_info_4" model="risk_management.risk.info">
            <field name="risk_category_id" ref="risk_management.risk_cat_4"/>
            <field name="subcategory">Cash flow</field>
            <field name="name">Company cashflow shortage</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    Inability of the company to meet its financial commitments, for lack of liquid cash.
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="cause" type="html">
                <ul>
                    <li>Poorly controlled need in working capital</li>
                    <li>Structural inadequacy of the upper part of the company's balance sheet</li>
                    <li>Lack of appropriate cash flow forecast</li>
                    <li>Significant delay in a customer payment</li>
                    <li>unavailability of suitable short-term financing solutions.</li>
                </ul>
            </field>
            <field name="consequence" type="html">
                <p>
                    Unpaid bills, cash-flow difficulties, which may lead to a situation of cessation of payments leading to the opening
                    of a bankruptcy or liquidation procedure.
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="control" type="html">
                <p>
                    Daily situation of the current cash position; cash flow forecasts; number of days and amounts of
                    anticipated overruns; rate and degree of use of short-term financing schemes
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="action" type="html">
                <p>
                    Development of a precise forecast of cash flow; absolute control of the need in working capital;
                    implementation of short term financing solutions (overdraft, factoring, discount); reinforcement of
                    equity; setting up an appropriate debt for long-term financing; current account contributions.

                </p>
            </field>
        </record>

    </data>
</odoo>