<odoo>
    <data>
        <!--Processes-->
        <record id="process00" model="risk_management.business_process">
            <field name="name">Planning</field>
            <field name="description">
                Thinking about the activities required to achieve a desired goal.
                It provides a systematic way of viewing problems and developing
                short- and long-term solutions. It involves the creation and maintenance of a plan.
            </field>
            <field name="process_type" eval="'M'"/>
        </record>

        <record id="process01" model="risk_management.business_process">
            <field name="name">Commercial</field>
            <field name="description">Production of quotes. Order Analysis and Validation</field>
        </record>

        <record id="process02" model="risk_management.business_process">
            <field name="name">outgoing logistics</field>
            <field name="description">control, packaging and shipping of goods sold.</field>
        </record>

        <!--Process Data-->
        <record id="data00" model="risk_management.business_process_data">
            <field name="name">Customer quote</field>
            <field name="int_provider_id" ref="process01"/>
        </record>
        <record id="data01" model="risk_management.business_process_data">
            <field name="name">Customer order form</field>
            <field name="int_provider_id" ref="process01"/>
        </record>
        <record id="data02" model="risk_management.business_process_data">
            <field name="name">Business plan</field>
            <field name="int_provider_id" ref="process00"/>
        </record>
        <record id="data03" model="risk_management.business_process_data">
            <field name="name">Marketing plan</field>
            <field name="int_provider_id" ref="process00"/>
        </record>

        <!-- TODO: add processes of all 3 types -->
        <!-- TODO: add demo data for project process using examples from PMBOK -->

        <!-- risk infos -->
        <record id="risk_info_1" model="risk_management.risk.info">
            <field name="risk_category_id" ref="risk_management.risk_cat_1"/>
            <field name="subcategory">Country Risk</field>
            <field name="name">Political instability (risk of war, terrorism, local conflict, attacks ...)</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>Risk of loss of business or profitability outside the company's natural boundary, due to geopolitical instability in the area of presence.</p>
            </field>
            <field name="cause" type="html">
                <p>War, terrorism, local conflict, bombing.</p>
            </field>
            <field name="consequence" type="html">
                <ul>
                    <li>Issues related to the safety of people and property. </li>
                    <li>Loss of turnover and/or profitability. </li>
                    <li>Economic and financial losses.</li>
                    <li>Reputational risk; risk of business failure.</li>
                </ul>
            </field>
            <field name="control" type="html">
               <p>
                   Monitor all geopolitical indicators available, from multiple sources (Ministries, Banks, International Institutions).
                Monitor local and regional situation, implement micromanagement on site.
               </p>
            </field>
            <field name="action" type="html">
                <p>
                    In-depth knowledge of the country concerned and its associated risks.
                Mastering the geopolitical issues of the geographical area of exposure.
                Reduction of the presence, repositioning of critical processes, exit of the zone,
                Avoidance strategy, reduction strategy.
                </p>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="risk_info_2" model="risk_management.risk.info">
            <field name="risk_category_id" ref="risk_management.risk_cat_2"/>
            <field name="subcategory">Cyclical risk</field>
            <field name="name">Unfavorable economic climate impacting the dynamics of the company's activity: inflation, slowdown, GDP decline, unemployment</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>Deteriorating economic conditions for carrying out business activities</p>
            </field>
            <field name="cause" type="html">
                <ul>
                    <li>Economic crisis of local, regional, national or global impact;</li>
                    <li>unemployment, decline in purchasing power B2B or B2C;</li>
                    <li>deterioration of public accounts, over-indebtedness, economic failure of a branch of activity.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="consequence" type="html">
                <ul>
                    <li>Loss of turnover, loss of business opportunities, loss of relative or absolute market shares.</li>
                    <li>Loss business development opportunity.</li>
                    <li>customer insolvency.</li>
                </ul>
            </field>
            <field name="control" type="html">
                <p>
                    Growth rate of the turnover. Turnover rate of the offer. Failure rate on launching new offers. Fine management
                of the company's activity levels (production, storage and consumption cycles)
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="action" type="html">
                <p>
                    Adaptability and flexibility of the strategic and production model of the company: reactivity of the supply
                the evolution of the demand, adaptation of the structure of production and cost of the offer; risk reduction
                strategy to be favored.
                </p>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="risk_info_3" model="risk_management.risk.info">
            <field name="risk_category_id" ref="risk_management.risk_cat_3"/>
            <field name="subcategory">Strategic model</field>
            <field name="name">
                Poor identification or poor definition of the strategic segments of the strategic business model
            </field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    Incorrect determination of the strategic business model segments to which the commercial offer is deployed.
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="cause" type="html">
                <ul>
                    <li>Bad knowledge of the market.</li>
                    <li>Bad segmentation of customers / prospects database.</li>
                    <li>Mismatch between Commercial offers and market demand.</li>
                </ul>
            </field>
            <field name="consequence" type="html">
                <ul>
                    <li>Inability to market the produced offers on the desired customer segments;</li>
                    <li>Loss of sales, deterioration of the company's economic conditions.</li>
                </ul>
            </field>
            <field name="control" type="html">
                <p>
                    Success rate of the marketing of the offer by strategic segment.
                Number of strategic segments.
                Dimensioning and validated consistency of the strategic business model
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="action" type="html">
                <p>
                    Precise analysis of target market, anticipated segments, and customer profiles making up each strategic segment.
                Precise identification of the specific needs of each client and consistency of the offer that is intended for them.
                Risk circumvention or reduction strategy.
                </p>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="risk_info_4" model="risk_management.risk.info">
            <field name="risk_category_id" ref="risk_management.risk_cat_4"/>
            <field name="subcategory">Cash flow</field>
            <field name="name">Company cashflow shortage</field>
            <field name="description" type="html">
                <p>
                    Inability of the company to meet its financial commitments, for lack of liquid cash.
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="cause" type="html">
                <ul>
                    <li>Poorly controlled need in working capital</li>
                    <li>Structural inadequacy of the upper part of the company's balance sheet</li>
                    <li>Lack of appropriate cash flow forecast</li>
                    <li>Significant delay in a customer payment</li>
                    <li>unavailability of suitable short-term financing solutions.</li>
                </ul>
            </field>
            <field name="consequence" type="html">
                <p>
                    Unpaid bills, cash-flow difficulties, which may lead to a situation of cessation of payments leading to the opening
                    of a bankruptcy or liquidation procedure.
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="control" type="html">
                <p>
                    Daily situation of the current cash position; cash flow forecasts; number of days and amounts of
                    anticipated overruns; rate and degree of use of short-term financing schemes
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="action" type="html">
                <p>
                    Development of a precise forecast of cash flow; absolute control of the need in working capital;
                    implementation of short term financing solutions (overdraft, factoring, discount); reinforcement of
                    equity; setting up an appropriate debt for long-term financing; current account contributions.

                </p>
            </field>
        </record>

    </data>
</odoo>